Activation is not a one-time event, it's a daily practice, it's the conscious choice
to filter your decisions through your M.V.P., it's the courage to embrace resistance as
training ground for your resilience and the wisdom to proactively plan to build your agility.
Your playbook for this lesson is filled with drills to help you put this concept into practice.
Take the time to work through the scenarios and stress test your own goals.
This is how you move from knowing to doing.
In our next lesson, we will focus on how to sustain the momentum, focusing on the critical
or A.R.A.W. pillar of wellbeing.
You have your blueprint and your game plan.
You are in the game.
You're ready.
You've got this.
Now, make it happen.
Head to your playbook and you'll see the next briefing.